We're now doing a
school-friendly makeup look for
14-year-olds.  First of all, I'd like to say that
you don't need to wear makeup at 14.
You are all so beautiful, of course.
First I have to take off these pimpel patches,
and it's important to know that we're
going to school, not a
club.  First and foremost, lip care is very important
.  Hi, why can't I open them
?
You didn't see that.  I
love Carix Cherry.  Mhm.  It tastes so
good.  At 14 I wouldn't
use foundation at all, but if you
have acne and feel uncomfortable and
want to cover it up, then use a
concealer.  I think the one from NYX is very
good, because it's simply skincare,
guys.  So, for example, I have here,
here, here.  And of course, you can also
cover your dark circles if they
bother you.  Okay, let's just ignore this for now.
Please ignore this. The
concealer is much too light for me. Use a
concealer in your skin tone.  Next,
we'll create a school-friendly
makeup look for 12-year-olds.  I look like
a corpse right now.  You would
look amazing.  Something else you can easily do at 14
is participate in something like this and
simply groom your eyebrows nicely
.  They would simply come into a nice shape
.  Please don't forget [ahem],
this is your life.  You can do whatever
you want.  The next and
final step is mascara.  Trust me,
my darlings, you don't need anything more than
concealer and mascara.  I love the
pink Eowtreme from Essence.  That was also
my very first makeup product and I
still love it today.  And that was it.
Which age should I
choose next?